基辅 乌克兰
地下拳击场
我对人与神都有罪
I have sinned against both man and God.
我在比地狱还阴暗的地牢中待了十年
I've spent ten years in a hole darker than hell.
一直在等待着
Waiting.. always waiting.
尽管我一直不明白这样生活的意义
I still do not know what this life is for.
也不明白我们选择如此生活的原因
Or why it's been given to us.
但我知道有人已经完成了我所追求的目标
And I know that a man has done what I've done..
尽管不值得去梦想
Does not deserve to dream.
但我依然在完成
But I still do.
加油 博伊卡
- Come on Boyka. - Boyka, Boyka!
加油啊 博伊卡
Yes! Come on, Boyka!
博伊卡加油
Bravo, Boyka!
高级监狱 俄罗斯
克什玛 克什玛 克什玛
准备好了吗  准备好了吗
Are you ready? Are you ready?
开始
Fight!
谢谢你 又是如此慷慨的捐赠
Another generous donation. Thank you.
这是我的荣幸
It is my pleasure.
你昨晚有没有赢得比赛  - 是的 我赢了 神父
- Did you win your last fight? - Yes, father, I did.
尤里 我们都很感激你一直以来的捐赠
Yuri... we are very grateful for all your donations
这些捐赠帮助我们建造了这个教堂
that help us build this church.
但如果你在自我救赎 暴力对你来说不是正确的途径
If it is salvation is you seek violence is not the answer.
但是我告诉过你 这只是一项运动 我们都得遵守游戏规则
But I told you. It's a sport. We have rules.
但你觉得上帝会接受
Even if you do have rules...
你的所作所为吗? 我觉得这是上帝赐予我的礼物
Do you think God approves of what you do?  - I think God gave me this gift.
如果我放弃了它 便是亵渎
And I think it would be a sin to waste it.
暴力会吞噬一个好人
Violence has a way of consuming men.
一旦被暴力吞噬
Then it is hard to see what good you can do..
人就会因此堕落
When you are surrounded by that.
基辅体育中心
博伊卡 好消息
Boyka, Boyka! Great news.
我终于找到了
I have found a fight. A real fight.
咱们一直以来梦寐以求的拳赛
The fight that you've wanted The fight that we've waited for.
是真正的比赛吗?  - 是真的
Legitimate fight. - Yes. And legal,
不像这种地下小拳赛
not like this underground shithole.
- 在哪里?  - 布达佩斯
- Where?  - Budapest.
争夺欧洲总冠军
It's A European divisional tournament.
下场比赛会来一位非常有实力的新拳手
I convinced the tournament scouts to come and watch you at your next fight.
如果你能说服他们，你就能参赛
If you convince them, then you're in!
真的这么简单 - 没错
- That's it? - Yes.
好极了
Very good!
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚我们迎来了重量级拳击赛
A qualification fight!
MMA倾情赞助
Sanctioned by the International Mixed Martial Arts Association.
本场冠军直接晋级欧洲总决赛
The winner of this fight. Will be competing at the European Championship.
比赛将在布达佩斯举行
That will be held in Budapest.
比赛拳手要坐在第一排
Boyka, the scouts are here, sitting in the front row.
- 好  - 感觉怎么样? 准备好了?  - 好了
- Good. - How are you feeling? Are you ready?  - I'm ready.
- 你紧张吗  - 不紧张
- Are you nervous? - No.
你的膝盖没关系吧  - 别问这么多问题
- How is you Knee? - Stop asking so many fucking questions.
我已经见过了你的对手
Before you go I must tell you. I've seen the other fighter
他很厉害
he's good.
我的对手都很厉害 最后还不是失败
They are all good. It does not matter.
可他不一样。我看得出来他很渴望比赛
This one's different. He is hungry. He fights like he needs it.
就像你一样
Like you.
没有谁可以阻碍我拿到冠军的步伐
Nothing, is going to stand in between me, and that tournament.
现在 请热烈欢迎我们的比赛队伍和拳手
And now we would like to welcome to our ring...Our own locked up hero.
打不倒的冠军
Our undisputed champion...
世界一流拳手
The most complete fighter in the world
尤里・博伊卡
Yuri Boyka..
博伊卡 博伊卡
Boyka! Boyka!
- 你好   - 这是我的同事
- Hello sir, this is my associate. - Good, to see you again.
先生们 比赛规则不再赘述
Alright, gentlemen. You've been over the rules.
请遵守规则 保护好自己
Protect yourselves at all times.
不许作弊
Follow my instructions. We gotta keep this clean.
现在请回到各自角落
Now.. go to your corner.
你还好吗  - 不行
- Are you alright? - No.
还可以吗？ 带好你的牙托
You okay, you okay? Take your mouthguard.
你不要再挣扎了
Stay the fuck down.
你做到了 博伊卡 我们赢定了 我说到做到
You did it, Boyka! We can go around the way.
我一直相信着你 看到这些观众了吗 他们爱你
I never ever doubted you. Come see this crowd, they love you.
恭喜你 博伊卡  - 非常令人深刻的拳技
- Congratulations, Boyka. - Very good, Boyka, very impressive.
我们很久没见到过像你这么优秀的拳手了
It's been a while since we have seen such an impressive fighter.
博伊卡 两周之后
Boyka, two weeks.
我们想让你参加布达佩斯的总决赛
We want to see you at the tournament in Budapest.
好 - 这是你唯一的机会
- Good. - So you know, this is your one shot.
如果你赢了 你就有资格进入大联盟 你要是输了 那就会失去一切
You win, and you're in the big league. You lose, and it's over.
我不会输 咱们到时候见
I don't lose, I'll be there.
好 那到时候见
Good. We'll see you there.
博伊卡 你这辈子就是为此而战 现在机会终于来了
Pretty great no? This is what you've been fighting for your whole life Boyka. Now it's here.
这是你今晚比赛的奖金
Your winnings from tonight's fight.
他怎么样了
What is the matter him?
他现在情况很不好 我们要马上送他去医院
He is in very serious condition, we are taking him to the hospital.
也许是脑震荡
It looks like a concussion.
但你觉得上帝会接受你的所作所为吗
Do you think God approves what you do?
我觉得这是上帝赐予我的礼物 如果我放弃了 便是亵渎
God gave me this gift. And it would be a shame to waste it.
给我滚出去
Get the fuck out.
- 什么事 博伊卡  - 昨天和我比赛的拳手
- What is it Boyka? - The man that I fought last night.
昨天被送到医院里了
They took him to the hospital.
他现在怎么样了
How is he doing?
你已经赢了 还在乎那个干什么
You won. What does it matter, how's he doing?
回答我的问题
Just answer the fucking question.
他死了
He is dead.
你这是什么意思
What do you mean he's dead?
这不是你的错 这是意外。你不用为此负责
Don't worry though. It was an accident. You are not liable for his death.
这是每个拳手必将承担的风险
It's a risk every fighter takes Boyka.
他叫什么名字  - 维克多
- What was his name? - Viktor.
维克多
Viktor...
他是哪里的人
where did he come from?
他是俄国人 来自多宁 只是一个拳手而已
He is a Russian from Drovny. He is just another fighter.
他有家人吗 有没有妻子和孩子
What about his family? Did he have a wife? Children?
我不清楚 我已经清理了他的更衣柜
How should I know? I cleaned out his locker.
博伊卡 别再纠结了
Forget about him Boyka.
给我看看他的行李
His things from the locker, I want to see them.
都在这个包里了
Here, I got his bag.
我已经检查过了 没有现金
He doesn't have any cash, I already checked.
我需要一本假护照 我要穿过俄罗斯边境
- I need a fake passport. - A fake passport for what? To cross the border.
可俄罗斯警方现在还在通缉你
I'm going to Russia. - Russia, Are you crazy? You are a wanted man there.
你就让我来解决吧  - 那布达佩斯呢？
- Let me worry about that. - And what about Budapest?
两周之后就要开赛了
Your dream? It's in less than 2 weeks.
你把护照帮我做好就行了 - 不行 你这是在犯错
- You give me the fucking passport or not? - I can't. It's a mistake.
你给还是不给
You get me the fucking passport.
当然 我会帮你做
Okay. Okay.
但我必须警告你
这可能会毁了你这一辈子 博伊卡
But I must warn you. This can ruin your life Boyka.
我不在乎
It's not this life I'm worried about.
多宁 俄罗斯
节哀顺变 - 谢谢
- My condolences. - Thank you.
谢谢你们
他是个好人 是个好拳手
He was a good man and a good fighter.
Yes.
你现在要怎么做  - 我从16岁起就和他在一块了
- What will you do now? - We have been together since I was 16.
我不知道该做什么 - 我说的不是这个
- I don't know anything else. - But this is not what I'm talking about.
这是我丈夫的葬礼 - 他已经死了 死人还有什么意义
- This is my husband's funeral. - He is dead. What does it matter now?
你现在可欠我很多钱呢
Except for the fact that you owe me, a lot of money.
我会为你工作偿还债务
I will work for you to pay off the loan.
我赚的每个子都是你的 - 不如让我来帮你
- You will get every ruble. - Let me help.
我会让你减轻一些负担
I can make things easier for you.
护照做好了吗？ - 你来晚了
- You get the passport? - You are late.
作为你的经纪人 我还是劝你…
As your manager, I advice you not to do this.
少废话
Just give me the fucking thing.
我阻止不了你  可我有一言还请你静听
Boyka, if I can't stop you, then, at least listen to me.
现在你习惯了自由的生活
You've gotten used to the outside,
所以回家路上要小心
You're going to have to be very careful going back.
不要乘坐公交大巴
Stay away from commercial buses.
大巴会载你去公交枢纽 那里都被严密监管着
Those will only take you to major border crossing with tight controls.
你最好坐当地的迷你巴士
Best bet is to get on a local minivan..
那些车会带你去军方的临时关卡
Assuming which will drive you across a provisional military checkpoint.
那里的士兵没有网络
The soldiers there, they have no internet access.
整体也比较松散
And generally they're relaxed and uninterested.
通过的时候保持低调 这样你才不会卷入麻烦当中
You keep your head down, and your nose clean..
一旦你进入俄罗斯 我就只能祝你好运了
And you should get through without any trouble. After that you're on your own.
拿出你们的护照来
Visas, passports, get them out..
都把护照准备好 你们配合工作才能快点结束
Have your papers ready. Nobody wants to wait on you.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
安东・拉格诺夫  - 你来乌克兰做什么
- Anton Lagunov. - What were you doing in Ukraine?
我来看我叔叔
Visiting my uncle.
他快不行了 你还有问题吗
He is dying. Is there a problem?
没问题  拿出护照来
No, no problem. Papers.
放行
多宁 俄罗斯
你有事吗
Can I help you?
我要和那个女的谈谈
I wanted to speak with her.
没人可以和她谈  - 他们去哪?
- Nobody speaks to her. - Where are they going?
她要去工作   - 在哪儿
- She's going to work now. - Where?
来啊
Come on!
伊戈尔 伊戈尔 伊戈尔
Igor, Igor!
今晚的冠军 依然是我们打不倒的
And the winner by TKO and still undefeated.
地下收割者 伊戈尔
Our underground killer, Igor!
这是我的赛场 混账们
This is my ring, you motherfuckers!
你们有意见吗
What was going to happen?
这是我的赛场
This is my ring!
你是谁 为什么跟踪我
Who are you? Are you following me?
不 我只是想和你谈谈
No. I need to talk to you.
什么事 我还在工作
About what? I am working.
求你了 我从大老远跑来 就是想和你谈谈
No, please. I'm sorry... I come very long way to talk to you.
你想干什么
What do you think you're doing?
继续工作
Get back to work.
你最好跟我来
Why don't you come with me?
我只是想和她谈谈
I just want to talk to her.
我们外面谈
Come on. We'll talk outside.
你找错人了 回家吧  给我几分钟就行
- You choose the wrong girl. Go home. - Look, I only need a few minutes with her.
她是老板的人 谁也不能碰她
She belongs to the boss. So fuck off.
她什么时候下班
So, what time does she finish work?
你是聋子吗
Are you deaf?
给他点颜色瞧瞧
Fuck this asshole up.
完美
Bravo.
完美的表演
Bravo. That was quite a show you put on.
我叫佐拉 这里是我开的
My name is Zourab. And this is my club.
你这身手应该帮我
You should fight for me.
在这打拳才对  - 我不感兴趣
Here, in my ring. - Not interested.
我来不是为了帮你比赛的  - 那你为什么要来
Didn't come here for that.  - Why did you come then?
我来是找那个女服务生说几句话
The girl. The waitress. I need to tell her something.
奥玛
Alma.
不管你要和她说什么 告诉我
Well, whatever it is you want to tell her, you can tell me,
- 我帮你传达   - 不用 我自己去
- I'll make sure that she gets the message. - No I give her the message myself.
没有我的允许 谁也不能接近她 她是我的
Nobody goes near Alma without my permission. I own her.
连这个城都是我的  如果你再去找她一次
I own this city. You try to talk to her one more time...
我就杀了你 别再让我看见你
I'll fucking kill you. Now get the hell out of my face.
快走
Go on.
盯紧他
Keep an eye on him.
我是全世界最一流的拳手
I am the most complete fighter in the world.
上帝会接受你的所作所为吗
Do you think God approves for what you do?
你以为想进就能进吗  站住
Hey. Where do you think you're going?  Hold it.
又是你 你想干什么
You again... what is it?
我只想过来告诉你
I came here today to tell you that...
我认识你丈夫 维克多  节哀顺变
I knew your husband, Victor. I'm sorry for your loss.
谢谢 麻烦你这么大老远来看我
Thank you. It's a very nice of you to come.
你老板 佐拉  有没有给你找麻烦
Your boss, Zourab... Does he bother you?
没有
No.
因为他借给我们的钱 我们才能经营这个体育中心
He gave Viktor and me a loan, so we could open this community center.
现在我得为他工作才能还债
I work just for him to pay off the debt.
你是在哪里见到维克多的
So, where did you meet Viktor?
你也是拳手吗  - 是的
- Are you a fighter too? - Yes, I'm a fighter.
我在基辅见到了他  你有没有看他最后一场比赛
- I met him in Kiev. - Then did you see his last fight?
是我做的
It was me.
当时在基辅和他比赛的人就是我
I was the one in the ring. In Kiev. It was an accident.
我只是想告诉你那是个意外  我能为你做些什么
I wanted to come here tell you that... If there is anything I can do..
你能 你确实可以帮我做些事情
Yes, yes, there is something you can do.
把他还给我 你能做到吗
Bring him back. Can you do this?
不能
No.
这是我那场比赛的奖金 你拿着
This is the money from the fight. I think you should have it.
这钱占满了我丈夫的血
This is blood money.
你就是为了这些钱才夺走我丈夫的性命吧
So that's why you took my husband's life. You murderer.
你还是自己留着享福吧 快走
Take these back and get the hell out of here.
回到基辅 从哪来的回哪去 快走
Back yo Kiev, or whatever it is, that you came from. Get out.
这些人还只是孩子 你这是在浪费我的时间
These are children in front of It's a waste of my fucking time.
奥莱克招了一个北方来的家伙
Olegs, just some new guy down from the north,
他想让我们去会会他
He says we have to see him.
他的人都是弱鸡 我需要真正的拳手
Oleg's guys are Minos. I need fucking sharks.
我们现在能找到的就这些人 你到底想要什么
This is what is available, Zourab. What do you want?
我想要什么
What do I Want?
我想要那种非凡的拳手 会战斗 会比赛
I want someone to impress me Slava. I want someone who knows how to hit. And someone who knows how to get hit.
而不是像他们有一样 整天只会打沙袋
Not these fucking bums you bring me from the streets.
这些打街拳的除了白吃饭什么都不会做
Who are merely piece of meat with a pulse.
你现在知道我想要什么了吧  找个让我服气的拳手
Slava, What I want, I want to be fucking entertained!
等等
Wait a minute.
我不是让你离开这里吗  - 你的屁话我才不会在乎
- Thought I told you to leave this town? - I don't give a shit you said.
那我的建议你考虑的怎么样了
Do you reconsider my offer?
奥玛 她欠你多少钱
How much does she owe you? Who, Alma.
这不关你的事  - 这现在就是我的事
- It is none of your fucking business. - Well, I'm making it my fucking business.
你肯定付不起
She owes me more than you can ever possibly pay.
那咱们来做个交易
Well, then I want to make a deal..
你放过她 我就为你比赛
I fight for you, you wipe her debt.
六场比赛 - 两场
- Six fights. - Deal.
三场
那到时候我们互不相欠
- Three fights. - And then she owes you nothing.
我只有一个条件 你要打败这里最强的拳手
One condition. You have to beat my champion.
你最好小心点 我会做掉你的
Watch out I'm going to fuck you up..
这个家伙我要最后一个收拾  - 好
- Just make sure you save this cunt to last. - Good.
明天就开始 比赛之间给我一天晚上休息的时间
We start tomorrow. A night's rest in between each.
一周三场比赛 你只要要输了一场…
Three fights a week. You really want to loose..
不会 我会速战速决
No. Just in a hurry.
有什么地方能让我训练
You have a place I can train?
有 五个街区外有个体育馆
Sure there is a gym five blocks east of here.
斯雷瓦会带你去
Slava here will show you.
还有最后一件事 和你做买卖非常愉快 尤里・博伊卡先生
One last thing. It's really nice to do business with you, Yuri Boyka.
很惊讶吧？ 我操持着这个镇
Oh, you surprised? I told you that it is my town.
有什么事是我不知道的 你不用担心警察找你麻烦
I know everything that comes to here. But don't worry about the police.
连他们都得向我汇报工作 你要记住一件事
They report to me. Just remember one thing.
我的地盘 要按我的规矩办事
My arena, my rules.
你不是告诉过我 不去找打街拳的吗
What are you doing? Someone bum off the street?
斯雷瓦 这可不是打街拳的
This is no bum off the street, Slava!
他来头大得很  什么来头
Don't you know a legend when he's punching you in the face? Him, what legend!
斯雷瓦 你不知道尤里・博伊卡吗
Slava... Don't you know who Yuri Boyka is?
博伊卡  我暂时还不能回去
- Boyka? - I have to stay longer.
你要待多久？ 一个星期左右  - 什么叫一个星期
- Longer? What do you mean? How much longer? - Maybe a week. What do you mean a week?
你已经等了这么久 付出了什么？
Do you how long you've waited? How much you've bled for this moment?
投入了这么多训练和金钱 你知不知道你在做什么
How much money you spent to fix your knee? Do you know what you're doing?
你只要改订车票就行了 到时候我会去的
Just change the fucking bus ticket. I'll be there.
我没叫你帮我  - 我想帮你
- I didn't ask you to fight for me. - I just want to help you.
我不想要你的钱还有你的帮助 你走就可以了
I don't want your help, I don't want your money. I just want you to leave me alone.
只要比赛一结束 我马上就走
I'll leave you alone as soon as I finish the fights.
至少让我偿还我对你和你丈夫欠下的债
It's the least I can do for you and your husband.
你想从我这里得到什么
What do you want from me?
- 我什么都不求  - 你以为我是奖品吗？
- I don't want anything from you. - Do you think I'm for sale?
- 赢了比赛我就是你的吗？  - 我没这个意思
- Someone can just win over in a fight? - I'm not fighting to own you.
只要债务还清 你就能重归自由
I'm fighting to pay your debts. So you can be free.
所以你跑这么大老远就是为了救我吗
So you came all this way to save me?
我是为自己的救赎而来
I come here to save myself.
奥玛 回到车上 该走了
Alma, get back in the car. It's time to go.
干什么？  - 你不许用我的沙袋
- What? - This is my fucking bag.
我一会就打完
It won't be long.
这是我的沙袋
I don't want you using it.
Hey!
该你上场了
It's time.
我们今晚迎来了新拳手 不要再吝惜你们手中的钞票
We have a new cover tonight, ladies and gentlemen. So place your bets.
红色角落出场的就是 尤里・博伊卡
In the red corner, a fierce contender. Yuri Boyka!
蓝色角落是来自我们小镇的拳手
In the blue corner a local boxer.
他的拳速极快还能置人于死地  他就是鲍里斯・塔索夫
He is quick. He is deadly. He is Boris Tarsov!
开始
Fight!
你也就逞一时威风 尤里・博伊卡
You can have your fun for now, Yuri Boyka.
你记住了 我才是这个赛场的主宰
But just remember, this is my ring.
和我预期的一样精彩 但别懈怠了
Well done. Nothing less than I expected. But don't get too comfortable.
第一关永远不会很难
First one is always easy.
给我们的赢家送杯水
Why don't you get our winner here a drink?
给你
Here..
你现在一定很渴  -谢谢
- You must be thirsty. - Thank you.
你知道这里有我能训练的地方吗
- You know a place where I can train? - Yes.
街上有一家体育馆
There is a gym down the street.
我去过了 里面的人都不是什么好东西
No that's place, it's covered down with rats.
跟我来体育中心 你可以在那训练
Come to the community center tomorrow. You can use the one there.
我现在给你老板干活 你还跟我过不去
I am fighting for your boss now. You're going to try stop me again?
地方不大 如果你喜欢你可以用
It's not much. But if you like it, you can use it.
很好
Very good.
别打扰他 他在训练
Hey stop bothering the man. Let him work.
没关系 让他们看吧
It's fine. It's okay. Let them stay.
你需要什么吗？  - 我只是来接水的
- Do you need something?  - Just needed water.
我训练是不是影响当你工作了
It's not bothering you there, the training?
没关系 我习惯了
No. I've missed it.
之前维克多一直在那训练 不分昼夜
Viktor never stopped training. Day or night.
女士们先生们 睁大你们的双眼
Ladies and gentlemen. Double your bets!
我们今晚安排了特别节目 让我们欢迎奥泽洛夫兄弟
Because we have something special for you tonight. The Ozerov brothers!
没错 女士们先生们 今晚的比赛是二对一
That's right, that's right. Ladies and gentlemen. Two against one.
带给你双重快感
Provides the fun!
我之前告诉你了 博伊卡 我的地盘 按我的规矩办事
Remember, Boyka! My arena, my rules.
让我看看你的本事吧
Now, let's see what you can do.
开始
Fight!
我希望你已经准备好了
I hope you're ready.
我会把他打成筛子
I've kicked their shit lot worse.
博伊卡
Boyka, Boyka!
今晚二对一比赛的冠军就是 博伊卡・尤里
And the winner by double knockout... Yuri Boyka!
克里奇夫 我的朋友
Kojtjev, my friend. Here..
去把那些嘴巴漏风的人除掉
Get rid of those who can't keep their mouth shut.
剩下的钱呢 是来干什么的 是我的一点小建议
- And the other stake, what's that for? - Proposition.
把克什玛尔送过来  - 克什玛尔 绰号叫梦魇的那个人？
- I want you to get me Koshmar. - Koshmar the nightmare?
就是他
I want him here.
不可能 我不可能把他送出监狱
It's impossible. I can't get him out of prison anymore.
上次我差点连饭碗都丢了  - 你可以做到
Last time almost cost me my job. - Yes you can.
不仅这些钱是你的 你还有奖品可以拿
You're not gonna just make more money. There is a bonus.
之前越狱的尤里・博伊卡 我可以送还给你
When I give you an escaped convict. Yuri Boyka.
我的丈夫也习惯在赛后训练
My husband used to train after matches too.
他说在肌肉酸痛的时候训练是最好的
He said that it was best time when the muscles still hurt.
拿着 这个东西可以治你的腰伤
Here, ointment for your back..
这是我祖母的祖传药
My grandmother's recipe.
给我吧 没事 我自己来 把它给我
Give it to me. It's fine I.. It's okay. Give it to me..
做下
Sit down.
你没必要这么为我拼命
You do not have to fight for me.
你随时都可以离开这个小镇
- You can leave this town anytime you want.
为什么你不选择离开
Why do not you leave here?
你只要带上你需要的东西 离开这里就好
Just take what you need, and get the hell out.
离开
To leave?
这个地方就是我们的梦想 就是这个中心
This place was our dream. This centrer...
这里的孩子们知道我们不会抛弃他们
The kids here know, I will never abandon them.
如果没有这个地方 事情只会变得更糟
Without a place like this, all of this kids will be in gangs or something worse.
你什么都不知道
But you probably won't know anything about it.
剩下的你自己拿着
You can keep the rest.
斯雷瓦 你有没有盯着博伊卡
Slava. Did your men watch Boyka?
有 我一直盯着他不放 他一直在那
Yes. Just like you said, for the whole time that he was there.
还有呢
And?
他每天训练两个小时 就离开了
He just trains. That's it. Two hours. Then he leaves.
奥玛呢 她也没什么  - 她一直忙自己的 不和他说话
- And she? What was she doing? - Nothing. She does not even talk to him.
连看都不怎么看他
She can barely even look at him.
你工作的太频繁了  - 我没得选择
- You work too hard. - I don't have a choice.
请你不要碰我  - 为什么？
- Please don't to touch me. - Why?
因为博伊卡吗？ 他在这待的时间太久了
Is it because of Boyka? I hear that he spends time here, too much time.
他只是需要一个地方训练而已
He just needs a place to train.
他是头野兽 一个冷血杀手 就是他杀了你的丈夫
He's an animal. A cold-blooded killer. The man that murdered your husband.
那是个意外 你真的相信吗？
That was an accident. Was it truly an accident?
就是他一拳一拳的打到你丈夫的脸上
When his fists pounded into your husband's skull.
一拳又一拳的打  - 你不要再说了
- Over and over and over. - Please, stop it.
事情不是你想的那样
It is not how it happened.
你已经和他上过床了吧
You fucking him, aren't you?
你怎么能这么说
How dare you?
你知道我多爱维克多 你马上给我离开
You know how much I loved Viktor. I want you to leave right now.
No.
求你放过我
Please let go off me.
他不应该来到这里 别再让他来 不然我杀了他
He is not allowed here. I'll fucking kill him, if you let him back in.
基里尔
Kiril?
博伊卡 体育馆里现在挤满了想要见你的粉丝
Boyka, the arena is already crawling with fans waiting to see you.
你的大名都登在了报纸和海报上
Your name has been published in all the newspaper and billboards.
别忘了今晚的公交车 9:45 出发
Don't forget, your bus is at 9:45 pm tonight.
别来玩了 媒体有很多事情要问你
Don't be late. The press is waiting to talk to you.
我会到的 别担心
Don't worry I will be there.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
有关你和我丈夫的拳赛 你告诉我他是怎么死的
The fight with my husband. Can you tell me what happened?
现在最好不要说这件事
I think it's better if we don't talk about it.
为什么？ 你是不是在隐瞒什么？
Why? Do you have something to hide?
我不想伤害你  - 没关系 我能接受
- I just don't want to hurt you. - I can take it.
看着我的眼睛 把真相告诉我
Look into my eyes and tell me the truth.
这究竟是不是意外
Was it really an accident?
我已经犯过了这样的错误 奥玛
I've done things in this life, Alma. Terrible things.
这个错误已经让我在监狱里待了很长时间
Things that put me in the prison for a long time.
我是个充满了仇恨 痛苦 又愤怒的人
I was a bitter, angry man, full of hate.
直到上帝给我指明道路 我看到希望
Until God showed me the path.
我已经走过了几百里
I've had hundreds of fights. Hundreds.
从最黑暗的拳击场到监狱里
In the shittiest of arenas to the darkest deepest hellhole prisons...
最邪恶的地狱
you could possibly imagine.
但我一直没抛下上帝赐予我的礼物
But I never lost sight of the gift God gave me.
直到有一天
And then one day...
上帝为我打开了大门 给我机会
God, he opened up the doors to me and gave me the chance
让我向全世界证明自己
to prove myself to the world.
他想考验我 我不想让他失望
He was testing me, and I was not going to disappoint him.
可是
And so...
我和维克多对打的时候
In the ring. With Viktor.
我看到的不是一个人
I did not see a man.
不是一位丈夫
I did not see a husband.
是阻挡在我和我的梦想之间的障碍
Only someone standing in between me and my dream.
可我没想杀死他
But I did not mean to kill him.
我很抱歉 我知道这些话减轻不了你的痛苦
I'm sorry. And I know it's not enough to take away your pain.
可我非常后悔 这种后悔直指我的心底
But I have regret it. I've regret it with all my soul.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen.
我们今晚安排的节目一定会让各位大饱眼福
We have a spectacular show for you tonight.
拿好你们手中的钞票 睁大你们的双眼
So place your bets and take your seats.
即将在红色角落走出来的是
In the red corner we have a fearsome fighter
一直以来战无不胜的尤里・博伊卡  让我听到你们的掌声
who's been undefeated so far, so, let's hear it for Yuri Boyka!
博伊卡 博伊卡 博伊卡
Boyka, Boyka! Boyka!
在蓝色角落中即将走出来的是
And in the blue corner... the big, bad man-killer...
一直以来战无不胜的地下拳赛终极兵器 伊戈尔・卡兹米尔
Our undisputed Drovny underground champion Igor Kazimir!
你已经死了
You're fucking dead!
伊戈尔 伊戈尔
Igor, Igor!
Fight!
欢迎来到我的世界 混蛋 还记得我说过的话吗
Welcome to my world motherfucker. You remember what I told you?
这是你的赛场 我记得呢  - 我会好好修理你
- Yes. Your ring. I know. - I'm going to fuck you.
Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
十分精彩的比赛 博伊卡
Very good fight, Boyka.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我要去赶公交车 一切都结束了 她现在自由了
I have a bust to catch. It's over. She is free.
什么叫结束了
What's over?
我们有言在先
We had a deal.
是的 三场比赛 并且要赢这里最好的拳手
Yes. The deal was three fights and you have to beat my champion.
那伊戈尔算什么
What does that fucking Igor look like to you?
他可不是这里最好的 他不过是个三流货色
Who? This guy? He is not my champion. He was your third fight.
现在你得挑战这里最好的拳手 别再扯淡了
Now you have to defeat my champion. This is fucking bullshit.
我不会再比赛了  - 你会的 博伊卡
- I am not fighting for you anymore. - Yes you are Boyka.
你不打 交易终止
Cause if you don't, then we don't have a deal.
难道你不想就她吗
Don't you want to save her?
你可以成为她的大英雄
Don't you want to be her hero?
如果你现在走掉 她还是要还债
You walk away now, and her debt still remains.
给我打 不然我就像卖垃圾一样卖掉她
Unless you want me to sell her like a piece of meat, you're going to fight.
如果你输了 那一切都结束了她就是我的
And after my champion crushes your skull. You and I will be done, and the girl will be mine.
你到车站了吗
Are you already at the bus station?
我还走不了  - 什么意思
- I can not leave yet. - Are you crazy? What is wrong with you?
你的车十五分钟之后就出发了   -  最后一班车是哪个
- Your bus leaves in 15 minutes. - What time is the last bus?
K1号 22点出发 如果你错过这班车 你会错过整场比赛的
10 pm. If you miss it, you won't get your flight to Budapest.
我会准时到的
I won't miss it.
还等什么啊
So what are we waiting for?
把你最好的拳手叫来吧
Bring me your fucking champion.
现在 我们请出今晚的特别嘉宾
And now for the main event of tonight..
他是监狱中的王牌 一头野兽
A true monster fresh out of prison.
让我们欢迎 梦魇 克什玛尔
Koshmar.. The nightmare!
开始
给克里奇夫打电话
Call Kojtjev.
佐拉  - 放开她
- Zourab! - Let go off me!
No!
你给不了我想要的 那这就是你的下场
This is what happens when you don't give me what I want.
你竟然选择一头野兽 一个杀人犯
You choose a murderer. An animal!
我说的还不清楚吗
Didn't I make it clear to you?
我有没有给过你机会 我给过你
Didn't I give you every fucking opportunity? Every opportunity I gave you.
你想看着他被杀吗
Now you wanna watch him die.
No!
把枪放下
Drop the gun. Drop it.
我们有言在先的 你个混蛋 放了她
We had a deal, you piece of shit. Let her go.
你知道你自己会是什么下场吗
And what? What do you think is gonna happen?
你只不过是个逃犯 博伊卡 你能给她什么？
You're an escaped convict, Boyka. What can you possibly give her?
你只是个可悲的拳手罢了 就像她死了的老公一样
You are a fucking washed up to beat fighter just like her fucking dead husband.
你受伤了 我得把你送到医院去
You're hurt. We have to get you to a doctor.
奥玛 我得问你一些事
Alma. I need to ask you something.
那天你问我 我想从你身上得到些什么
The day you came to see me, you asked me what it was I wanted from you.
我不知道怎么回答
I did not know how to say it at that time...
可我只想求得你的原谅
But I needed to ask you for your forgiveness.
原谅我对你丈夫做的那些事
For what I did to your husband.
走吧 我们还有机会离开这 求你了
Come on. We can still get you out of here. Please.
不 我得知道
No. I need to know.
你能不能原谅我
Can you forgive me?
尤里・博伊卡 你被捕了
Yuri Boyka. You are under arrest.
求你原谅我
Do you forgive me? 408.
高级监狱 俄罗斯
六个月后
很高兴又见到你了 尤里 最近好吗
It's good to see you, Yuri. How have you been?
我很好 我没想到你会来看我
I'm fine. I did not expect to see you.
孩子们还好吗？ - 他们很好
- How are the kids? - They are doing great.
这是他们为你画的画
They drew these pictures for you.
抱歉 我本来能早点过来看你的 可是我来不了
I'm sorry. I wanted to come visit earlier, but I couldn't.
我只是还没准备好  - 我能理解
- I wasn't ready. - I understand.
我第一次见你的时候 我根本不知道该说什么 做什么
When I first saw you, I did not know what to say or do.
愤怒使我迷失了自己
I was too angry. I was... lost.
但是你让我知道
But then you showed me something.
这个世界上还是有善意的
You've showed me that there was still good in the world.
所以我今天来
That's why I came here today.
是为了谢谢你 尤里
To thank you, Yuri.
因为你替我拿回了尊严和自由
For giving me back my dignity, my freedom.
还有 我原谅你了
And because I you to know that... I forgive you.
谢谢
Thank you.
Boyka, Boyka, Boyka!
博伊卡 博伊卡 博伊卡
缅怀 丹尼・勒纳
（知名动作电影制片人 作品包括
《敢死队》系列 《奥林匹斯的陷落》等）